Yokubjon Mukhamedov



ekubmuhamedov@gmail.com



+998971972822



linkedin.com/in/jacob-mukhamedov-0075a71aa

Summary

Crafting beautiful, functional, and user-friendly mobile applications is my calling as a Flutter developer with 3 years of experience. I have honed my skills both in collaborative team settings and as a solo developer, delivering top-notch results every time. I take pride in my commitment to clean code and comprehensive documentation, ensuring that every project I work on is not only a success today, but also maintainable and scalable for the future. Let's create something amazing together.

Programming Languages: Dart, Kotlin, Java, Bash

Technologies: Flutter, WebSocket, WebRTC, REST API, Docker, PWA

Tools: Npm, Pub, Jira, YouTrack, Swagger

Source Control: Git, Gitlab, Github Methodology: Scrum, Agile, TDD Databases: NoSQL, SQLite, CI/CD: GitLab, GitHub, Fastlane

Languages:

- English: full professional proficiency - Russian: native or bilingual proficiency - Uzbek: limited working proficiency

Experience



Flutter Developer

Ptolemay LLC Aug 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months)



► Flutter Developer

OX Group Jun 2020 - Sep 2020 (4 months) Junior Flutter Developer

Education



INHA University in Tashkent

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science and Engineering 2019 - 2023

Licenses & Certifications



Flutter & Dart - The Complete Guide [2020 Edition] - Udemy

UC-ba9702b7-9f36-4d77-8ce2-317aaab66153



The Complete Flutter Development Bootcamp - The App Brewery

cert_h456f9tm

Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) • Flutter • Dart • REST APIs • Git • Docker Products • NoSQL